[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where is Western University located?", "correct_answer": "Baku, Azerbaijan", "incorrect_answers": ["Gunninson, Colorado", "Washington, DC", "Holland, Michigan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Do Giant Pandas hibernate?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What valley in California is referenced in Jack Londons novel The Valley of the Moon?", "correct_answer": "Sonoma Valley", "incorrect_answers": ["Death Valley", "Sierra Valley", "Deep Springs Valley"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 2000 comedy movie Me, Myself  Irene, starring Jim Carrey and Renee Zellweger, Hank had plastic surgery to change this part of his body.", "correct_answer": "Chin", "incorrect_answers": ["Buttocks", "Lips", "Nose"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following planets is closest to the Sun?", "correct_answer": "Mercury", "incorrect_answers": ["Venus", "Mars", "Earth"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the warring group in Blood Diamond that invades the village and takes away the fisherman and his son.", "correct_answer": "R.U.F.", "incorrect_answers": ["S.L.R.P.", "C.R.F.", "S.R.U.F."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which line the food is not matched with its place of origin?", "correct_answer": "Peach - Peru", "incorrect_answers": ["Spinach - Iran", "Grapefruit - Barbados", "Blueberry - North America"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Chinchillas have a wide range of hearing - 5 Hz to 60 kHz", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1989 Winona Ryder teamed up with Christian Slater and Jeremy Applegate to star in this movie.", "correct_answer": "Heathers", "incorrect_answers": ["The Breakfast Club", "K-9", "Dont Tell Mom the Babysitter is dead"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "While the number of storms in the Atlantic has increased in past years, this does not seem to be a global trend.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Jell-O, the popular gelatin dessert, is made in part, from what?", "correct_answer": "Bones and hides", "incorrect_answers": ["Red ants", "None of these", "Horses and cows hooves"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Actress Butterfly McQueen never got her high school diploma.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]